

#### Summary

Dynamic and motivated individual with strong customer service skills. Known for creating enjoyable experiences, building positive relationships with clients, and adapting quickly to new challenges. Enthusiastic about delivering exceptional service and contributing to a welcoming environment.

#### Skills

- ReactJs / JavaScript / Node.js
- UI/UX Design
- Linux
- TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, ICP
- Database Management
- Network Troubleshooting
- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork
- Multitasking
- Adaptability
- Customer Service
- Learning Agility
- Autonomous
- · Excellent customer service
- Inventory and stock management

## languages

**English**: Fluent

French: Fluent

**German**: Basics

Malagasy: Native

# TOJONIRINA HASINIAINA ELIE JOSEPH MARCELLIN

**Phone** 

+973 3420 1786

+973 3828 9186

**Email** 

tnr.hasiniaina@outlook.com

**Address** 

257 Amwaj Island , Muharraq Bahrain

### **Experience**

#### Internship Trainee - Food & Beverage Jul 2024 - Dec 2024 Address Beach Resort - Bahrain

- Assisted in preparing and serving beverages, including mocktails, cocktails.
- Provided excellent guest service by meeting preferences
- Supported daily operations by restocking supplies and maintaining cleanliness
- Operated and troubleshot Micros and POS systems for order processing
- Collaborated with the team to ensure smooth service during peak hours
- Handled guest inquiries and resolved issues
- Managed stock levels and restocking needs
- Attended F&B training sessions
- Suggested premium beverages to enhance guest experience
- Followed health and safety regulations in food and beverage preparation

#### Full Stack Web Developer Intern Mar 2023 – Nov 2023 Ministry of Interior and Decentralization

- Conducted IT maintenance tasks, including hardware and software configuration, as well as installation and management of systems.
- $\bullet \ {\sf Administered} \ {\sf and} \ {\sf troubleshot} \ {\sf local} \ {\sf area} \ {\sf networks} \ ({\sf LAN}) \ {\sf to} \ {\sf maintain} \ {\sf smooth} \ {\sf connectivity}. \\$
- Performed thorough testing (unit and integration tests) to identify and fix bugs.
- Documented development processes and provided training to end us

# Technical Support Agent – ADSL Jun 2021 – Dec 2021 Intelcia , SFR France

- Provided technical support and assistance via phone, email, and chat.
- Educated customers on SFR products, services, and features.
- Documented customer interactions and resolutions in the CRM system.
- Created tickets during generic incidents to facilitate quick resolution.

# **Education**

Bachelor of Science Mar 2020 – Nov 2023

IS-INFO University

Bachelor's degree in computer science

High School Degree 2018

Collège Saint Philippe et Jacques

Technical Baccalaureate in Management and Accounting

Vocational Studies Diploma 2017 Collège Saint Philippe et Jacques

Management and Accounting